## **OLOKEOGUN, KEMI SOGO**

Ladigbolu Area, Oyo, Oyo State. **Mobile:** +234 806 382 0762 **Email:** kemi8olokeogun@gmail.com

### **Career Objective**

A driven, self-motivated graduate of philosophy with a keen eye for service delivery coupled with endless possibilities that lie within and its ability to create value. I am a vibrant young man who is an enthusiastic team player, demonstrating high level of passion and accuracy during research. I adapt fast to changing environments and I am always ready and willing to learn new skills for achieving excellent results.

## **Core Competencies**

• Time Management.

Interpersonal Skills.

• Team Player.

Team Building/Peacebuilding.

• Project/Team Management.

Analytical Thinking.

## **Work Experience**

## **Administrative Officer/HMO Desk Officer**

Shekinah Medical Centre, Owode Oyo.

Dec 2021 - Till Date

- Serve as a liaison among healthcare facility board, healthcare management organizations, and NHIS enrollees.
- Oversee the development and implementation of programs and policies for patient services, quality assurance, public relations, and department activities.
- Assist with recruitment, screening, and enrolment of personnel.

#### **Head Teacher**

Olayinka Model Schools, Ladigbolu Area, Oyo.

Mar 2021 – Sept 2021

- Evaluated and documented students' progress.
- Allocated and graded homework, assignments and tests.
- Observed individual student performance and reported observation to parents and school administrators.
- Prepared and organized class activities to supplement teaching materials.
- Organized and participated in extracurricular activities such as outings, social activities and sporting events.

### Ad-hoc Staff (APO II)

Independent Electoral Commission (INEC).

2018

- Assisted with the collection of materials from SPO.
- Helped in confirming details of the PVC on the registers of voters.
- Assisted in applying indelible ink.
- Helped in completing Form EC 40H.

## **English Language Subject Teacher (NYSC)**

L.A. Secondary Grammar School, Ipetumodu, Osun State. Jan 2015 - Nov 2015

- Served as a subject teacher in charge of student lessons in English language.
- Created student syllabus, outlines and lesson notes on the subject.
- Administered tests and marked assessments and examination scripts.
- Gained a 61.3%improvement in English Language scores during term exams for the year.
- Participated actively in core-curricular activities to aid social developments in students.

#### **Education**

• M.A. Peace and Conflict Studies
University of Ibadan, Ibadan, Oyo State.

• B.A. Philosophy
Obafemi Awolowo University, Ile-Ife, Osun State.

## **Professional Certification**

West Africa Peace Ambassadors Network (WAPAN) 2018
Participant

• Certificate in Conflict Resolution and Peacebuilding

# Society for Peace Studies and Practice Participant

Certificate in Conflict Analysis, Project Design and Management

## **Technical and Software Skills**

2018

• Basic Proficiency: Microsoft Office: PowerPoint, Word and Excel.

#### Reference

#### Dr Adeola Adams +234 708 147 8381

Institute for Peace and Strategic Studies, <a href="mailto:adadams@noun.edu.ng">adadams@noun.edu.ng</a>
University Ibadan, Ibadan,
Oyo State.

#### Mr. Olakunle Afolabi +234 703 078 7167

Banking, johnkunz\_afolabi@yahoo.com First Bank of Nigeria Limited, 35 Marina, Lagos State.